<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tech.hanke.se</title>
    <link>https://tech.hanke.se/</link>
    <description>Recent content on tech.hanke.se</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 17:01:26 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tech.hanke.se/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>It All Started With an Ey</title>
      <link>https://tech.hanke.se/posts/it-all-started-with-an-ey/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 17:01:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech.hanke.se/posts/it-all-started-with-an-ey/</guid>
      <description>ey Is the start of all bearer tokens when accessing APIs and similar resources. I have not really been thinking about it much until I realized that tokens are Base64 encoded JSON objects.
JSON objects allways start with an { to encapsulate the contents of the object, so it makes sense that all tokens start with the same.
Just thought that was a fun fact when I thought of it, so why not put it out there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Issuer Hell</title>
      <link>https://tech.hanke.se/posts/issuer-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 13:01:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech.hanke.se/posts/issuer-hell/</guid>
      <description>Self referencing meta post This whole post is about setting up the infrastructure around this site.
While doing so I was wrestling the certificate issuing process for quite some time. But to arrive at the problem, and eventually the solution, we have to go back a bit.
The building blocks Before you can serve a site correctly in Kubernetes there are a set of resources that have to be set up correctly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://tech.hanke.se/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 12:07:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tech.hanke.se/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>What? I feel like starting a simple blog where I can write about projects I am working on, problems I run in to, and eventually the solutions to those problems. I will also be writing about any tips, tricks and cool tools I run in to throughout the process.
Why? To be honest, I do not expect anyone to be reading this at all. I just want some place to write about technology that excite and sometimes annoy me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
